epicgameads.com 2011-12-01

# Epic Game Ads

EGA PUBLISHING PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 1, 2011.

At Epic Game Ads ("EGA"), we represent online publishers and their properties ("Publisher Properties") to advertisers and support other properties sponsored by advertiser clients ("Client-Sponsored Properties"). Because we understand the importance of your privacy, we take safeguarding your personal information very seriously. We are providing the following Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of the personally identifiable information collected from you during your use of any EGA website whether from (i) a Client-Sponsored Property or other website on epicgameads.com (the "EGA Domain") (such as the Epic Game Ads home page at (http://www.epicgameads.com/)) or (ii) a Client-Sponsored Property on a different domain (each a "Site" together our "Sites"). You'll know you're on one of our Sites because a version of this Privacy Policy will be posted.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new policy on each Site and highlighting the changes. We suggest that you consult an EGA Site regularly to check for any changes to this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at support@epicgameads.com

Information We Collect

We collect information in connection with our Sites and Services in the following circumstances, though not every one of our Sites offers each of these four: (i) registering for an account, (ii) participation in surveys, sweepstakes, contests, and promotions ("Surveys and Promotions"), (iii) contacting EGA, and (iv) visiting and browsing any of our Sites.

Registration

Information collected during the registration process may include your name, company name, company address, phone number, username, email address, date of birth, account password. We may also collect your IP address when you register and use the Site. Note that you must register on the EGA Domain in order to become an EGA advertiser for the Publisher Properties. From time to time in the future we may offer additional features, services, and promotional opportunities that may require you to submit additional information to participate.

Surveys and Promotions

We also collect certain information about you and your web browsing sessions if you participate in Surveys and Promotions, which allows EGA to coordinate the marketing support that allows EGA publishers to continue to share their knowledge, insights, and opinions. Participation in Surveys and Promotions is optional. Should you choose to participate, the information we collect for Surveys and Promotions may include your name, phone number, address, e-mail address, IP address, website from whence you came to the applicable Site, travel preferences, favorite websites, family profile, age, whether you are a U.S. resident, and employment profile.

Contacting EGA

You may also contact EGA by filling out and submitting a form through a Site, or by submitting feedback when you are logged in to a Site. When you contact EGA through a Site, your full name and email address are transmitted to EGA. Any other information you choose to include in the form you submit would also be transferred to and stored on EGA's servers.

Anonymous Information

We also collect "Anonymous Information", such as traffic statistics and general usage patterns regarding page views, dates and times you use the Site, the website that referred you to the Site, and the method by which you accessed the Site, files accessed through the Site, responses sent to the browser, the length of data sent to the browser, and other data used in the communication between browser and Sites. EGA does not use cookies to collect information about your activities on any of our Sites.

How We Use the Information we Collect

We call information you provide that can be used to locate or identify you "Personally Identifiable Information." We use it to provide our Services and to communicate with you regarding such Services. We may also use your Personally Identifiable Information to provide information you have requested or products you have purchased (e.g., membership updates, e-mail newsletters, advertising insertion orders), to resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems. We also may use your Personally Identifiable Information: to respond to specific inquiries made by you; to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Use; and to customize, measure, and improve our Services, content, and layout. In addition, the EGA Network analyzes and uses your Personally Identifiable Information and supplements it with other information we obtain to notify you and target advertising to you regarding special offers, products, services, and information that we think may be of interest to you, and to measure the advertising effectiveness of advertisements on our Sites and Publisher Properties.

We use your Anonymous Information for the purposes of system administration, providing certain site functionality and content, targeted advertising, site tracking, and collecting and reporting aggregate usage information. We may combine Anonymous Information with your personally identifiable information to notify you of special offers and target advertising and other content to you.

Phishing

We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your username, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to EGA. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is our top priority. For more information about phishing, you may want to visit the Federal Trade Commission's website at http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/alerts phishingalrt.htm.

Information Sharing

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties.

Posting

Any information voluntarily disclosed by users and posted on our site (on message boards, web logs, and/or in chat areas) may be viewed and used by others. If you post personal information that is accessible to the public online, you do so at your own risk. Be aware that you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Third Party Service Providers

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform various functions and provide services to us (for example, web hosting services and maintenance services). These third parties may have access to some of your Personally Identifiable Information, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your Personally Identifiable Information.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

We may choose to disclose some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information to the government, law enforcement officials, or private parties if we, in our sole discretion, believe it necessary or appropriate to comply with the law, to respond to legal complaints, to comply with legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the rights of EGA or a third party, to ensure the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally questionable activity.

Changes in Corporate Ownership

If any or all of the assets of EGA are acquired by, or merged with, another entity we will share some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information with that entity.

Accessing and Changing Your Information

You may always access and modify certain of your Personally Identifiable Information you provide through EGA's self-service e-commerce platform by visiting the "sign in" area at the EGA Domain. You may or may not be able to modify the Personally Identifiable Information you provide through other parts of the EGA Domain or other Sites. If this causes concern, please contact us at the e-mail address provided below and we will provide information for the specific Site you reference.

Security

We place great importance on the safety and security of your Personally Identifiable Information. We employ certain physical, procedural, and technological measures in an attempt to protect your Personally Identifiable Information from unauthorized access and use. FM's servers that contain Personally Identifiable Information are stored in an off-site facility. EGA also uses hashed passwords, which allows an algorithmic version of your password to be stored instead of you actual password. When receiving financial information (e.g., PayPal account IDs) for completing certain online transactions, including those in connection with the EGA self-service platform, our site uses SSL or "Secure Sockets Layer," an industry standard security protocol, though other communications through the Sites are not encrypted. Although we do attempt to keep your Personally Identifiable Information secure, no security measures are perfect; there is always a possibility that a security breach could occur, resulting in the release of Personally Identifiable Information.

Links to Other Sites

Each EGA Site may contain links to other websites, in several places. You should pay particular attention to which website you are visiting when submitting any personally identifiable information to these websites. This Privacy Policy addresses the use and disclosure of only that information that we collect from you through our various Sites. Different rules may apply to information you submit to other websites including Publisher Properties, and we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these websites.

Our Policy Toward Children

None of our Sites are directed toward persons under eighteen years of age. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at support@epicgameads.com . If we become aware that a child under thirteen has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will remove such information from our files.
